Oh, no .
Then there's a win.
This will be his greatest win.
Life will lose another win.
This will get the win.
I have its own trip.
Do it short about the public mission of the world?
See you later!
Come welcome...
Let's go
We!
Are you going to make it better?
Then do not wear it to me, Bell.
Yes,guysDel dig.
Ugh!
I can say I'll tell you.
I give you a statement here this way, and see what she will see.
All right. Let's rewind.
Would you please watchante which?
Something like this
Oi, あんたは リトルルゥーキーか?
Ah...
So much.
U estamos torrent Done You
Gat ре
負けんな!
Ah...
And the fact iseminine
inch ok
ASON Ethereumfden!
SILESO SHIMO
危ないですよ
これは…!
god is that out with fear
I can make you like this dream gifted
Please stay in my YouTube
I'm in fondo machine
Yes
충
I brought back to eve
I wish you
How did you go?
Hmm...
He was just waiting to win, but it's a game
It's not available
You're full of sea
Cruises
activity
We'll sing it again?
I will win a question
víum
In the pastverstands we had him
Y toussが無事なら勝ち
その間に敵対象を倒しても勝ち
こんな条件で負けるはずないでしょ
でも お願いだから信じて ダフネちゃん
それで最後よ 縄文を閉めて
だめ あれを入れてしまったら…
おい 待て!待てったら!
うううっ
Cool, yay!
Can you get there?
How would you do that,ya?
You can't marvel, lookingют at that.
How old are you?
All you have to you, when you have it.
What?
What is that?
I only have one thing.
Soho tall!
They're all over.
They picked up.
Everyone, good morning!
We're going to have the U.O. Game Day!
We're going to be a leader of the Ivory Archer!
The name is Fire Inferno Frame!
We're going to be here!
We're going to be the main character of Ganesha!
Ganesha, please!
I'm a Ganesha!
Yes, sir!
Wow! I got it! I got it!
I got it!
The War Game is an O'Rario.
It's a good thing.
Well, it's a good thing.
Oh.
Apollon, come here.
Estia.
You're going to have a break-up.
You're going to have to be sold wildly.
Oh.
Have you got it, Kaiko?
Let's talk to Etwa!
Huh?
Your home!
I went over here.
So, I'll let you try.
At the moment, I want to be kepada the Dragon DragonDE.
Your standalone flight of Crafts!
Colonel Holo.
Pretty much.
The end of the year
I'm not a man!
Are you okay?
Look at that!
あっ…
アイズ! 始まるよ!
さあ! ただいま正午となりました!
ウオーゲーム開始です!
始まったな
とはいえ3日もある
いきなり仕掛けたわ
は?
あれは…
もう来ただと!
だがたった1人だ!
馬鹿め!
はっ!
なんと! 開幕速攻だ!
あれはもしや魔剣か!
なるほど 悪くない手だ
しかし こちらの兵力は100以上
君たちはわずか5人
あの程度で戦力差が埋まるかな?
クロッゾの魔剣
まさか私がこれを使う日が来るとは
はっ!
さあ 出てきなさい!
くそ! 外はどうなってる?
負けだ! 負けで攻撃されてる!
何?
ヒュアキントスからの命令だ!
50人出撃して外のやつを倒しに行けって!
50だと! 兵の半分だと!
半端な数じゃ あの魔剣に吹き飛ばされちまう!
使ってんのは1人だ!
倒してさっさく戻ってくればいいだろ!
うっ!
うっ! 早く行けよ!
うっ… やむを得ん… 出るぞ!
ふっ!
うっ!
うっ…
魔剣が砕けたぞ!
今だ! やつえ!
はっ…
エルフだと…
駆け巻くも賢き いかなるものも打ち破る我が神よ
尊き天よりの導きよ
敵が入り込んだぞ!
キュアキントスを直接狙う気だ!
誰でもいい! 止めろ!
貴様…
エルフでありながら同胞の里を焼いた 忌々しき魔剣を使うなど恥をしれ!
うっ!
あいにく 私には一族の恩衆より大切なものがある
友を助けるのが恥だというのなら
いくらでも甘んじましょう!
ぐっ! あっ!
強い!
怯むな! 一気に行くぞ!
天より至り 血を据えよ!
天より至り 血を据えよ
うーん…
うーん!
うああっ!
はっ!
おおっ!
はああっ!
神武統制!
普通の見た目!
はああっ!
しばらく…
自分と付き合ってもらいます!
これは重力魔法!?
寄ってきた敵が釘付けた!
このタイミングでの自爆攻撃!
どうですか ガネーシャ様!
俺がガネーシャだ!
真面目にやってくれませんかね!
気張れよ 美琴
おおっ!
タケントコ イタゴ すげえじゃん!
覆面の冒険者は 一体何で呼んなんだ?
しっ!
早すぎるな
何がですか?
アポロン側の動きがさ
魔剣へのカウンターも 美琴ちゃんへの対応も
全てが早すぎる
はっ…
まさか 誘導されているのですか?
戦いの中で情報は武器だ
入手するのが早いほど 最高の切り札になる
ただし もしその中に毒が混ざっていたとすれば
全身に巡るのもまた早い
たった一滴の毒が 取り返しもつかない激薬になるぜ
激薬になるぜ
はっ…
ルーは何をやっている?
よっ うまく化けたな
本当にお疲れさま リリー
さあ 行ってください
リリーはもう少しかき回しておきます
うっ…
あっ!
裏切りだー!
なんと アポロンファミリアから 裏切り者が出た!
んー… ルーアンめ…
フフッ…
んー…
あっ…
はあ?
敵が?
いつの間に どうやって 入り込まれたのよ?
そ… そこまでは…
たく…
とにかく この空中廊下を 渡らせないわ
魔導士 栄章を準備
弓使いは前に うちの合図で 制作よ!
敵対象は塔の上だ
行け ベル
放て!
燃え尽きろ! 下砲の技!
うわああっ!
まあ 待てよ
あっ…
冒険者だったら これでやろうぜ
なあ
すごいね アイズム!
アルゴノートくん 大将の イルトウムで来ちゃった!
んっ…
でも 魔剣があるなら 最初からそれを持って塔に突っ込めばいいのに
ウサギ野郎は てめえの力で 蹴りをつけてえだけだろ
オスだぞ あいつは
けっ… なんたる集大
アポロン様に顔向けできんぞ
団長様 団長様 ここから逃げてください
逃げてください
だが あれが 単身攻め込んできたところで 敵ではない
どうか聞いてください
お願いですから 早く逃げて…
黙っていろ!
奴が入ってきたところを 一気に叩け!
だが 殺すなよ
殺すなよ 止めは私が刺す
はあ…
響く中二時のお告げ
塔へ急げ!
な… 誰だ!
うっ…
はあ…
うっ… 魔法が消えたぞ
やっちまう!
うっ…
はあ…
くっ… まだまだ!
うっ…
みんなの力で ここまで来られた
ここからは…
僕が!
ああ…
くっ…
雷が昇る…
ファイアバルト!
何だと!
ああ!
はあ…
うお…
アハ!
何だろ!
何だと!
くっ…
こんなことが…
That's what I'm going to do!
Huh?
Uh-oh!
Bacana!
早すぎる!
以前戦った時とはまるで…
誰だ?
お前は!
Uh-oh!
我が名は愛、光の長寿!
我が太陽にこの身を捧ぐ!
かなしてください!
花つ花輪の一刀
来たれ西方の風!
アロデピオス!
セル様の弾をさせません!
うっ!
自動追尾!
アハハハ! 逃げられんぞ!
うっ!
ファイアボルト!
無駄だ!
ルーベルー!
プリカルルル!
No.
What?
Oh...
...
That's enough for that.
But what are you裝ps...
Stay for that!
une bathing at her eyes, the moves are simple.
I am here assez.
The lastaría of time is my tonne.
The first one isற.
edorahığah!
GLAH!!
McLuh!!
ềuah!!
ELLAH!!
.
The game is called FESTIA FAMILIA!
Are you baik that you want here?
BELLさん…
… I can't
I can't win!
Really, will be housing or Rather…
Where do you could be sure?
Where are you going!
Dungeon?
Dungeon, crazy?
Dungeon.
Thank you, Belle
So...
That...
The supernatural...
You can compton and you need to cut out
When do you sign?
The obligatory mask is there!
You are so cute!
Trying to be
Go!
I'm being told that I astonished you
.
The most pile of possessions have a AngstLEY
, and you may not consider a
.
All of these rewards will keep you safe.
Actually, we're left to try now.
Then we'll make a codec for everything you can have, but…
Let's go.
N i'v SB Nご rendon,
Ryu2sang
thank you
and then
Lily
I really really thank you
Bye...
And Lily Thanks foriani
So I'll go home
The
アポロファミリアのお屋敷 乗っ取っちゃったんですね
前のホームは理不尽に潰されたんだ 文句は言わせないぞ
はあ
いざ いろいろやることはあるけど まずはこれだ
フィッ フィッ
ん?
これは 炎?
ヘスティア様の象徴 守り火ですね
それと 鐘か?
鐘? ベル?
つまり ヘスティア様とベル様!
フフフ その通り!
今日からこれが 僕たちのエンブレムだ!
はあ
えいっ
Next time, HOME.